Did you know there are more people
with genius IQs living in China
than there are people of any kind
living in the United States?
- That can't possibly be true.
- It is.
What would account for that?
Well, first, an awful lot of people
live in China, but here's my question.
How do you distinguish yourself
in a population of people
who all got 1600 on their SATs?
- I didn't know they take SATs in China.
- They don't.
I wasn't talking about China anymore,
I was talking about me.
You got a 1600?
Yes. I could sing in an a Capella group,
but I can't sing.
Does that mean you actually
got nothing wrong?
I could row crew or invent a $25 PC.
Or you could get into a final club.
Or I get into a final club.
You know, from a woman's perspective,
sometimes not singing in
an a Capella group is a good thing.
This is serious.
On the other hand,
I do like guys who row crew.
Well, I can't do that.
I was kidding.
And, yes, I got nothing wrong on the test.
- Have you ever tried?
- I'm trying right now.
- To row crew?
- To get into a final club.
To row crew? No.
Are you, like, whatever, delusional?
Maybe it's just sometimes
you say two things at once.
I'm not sure which one
I'm supposed to be aiming at.
But you've seen guys who row crew, right?
No.
Okay, well, they're bigger than me.
They're world-class athletes.
And a second ago,
you said you like guys who row crew
so I assumed you had met one.
I guess I just meant I like the idea of it.
You know, the way a girl likes cowboys.
Okay.